Hello hello everyone I am Krishna Churna,
one of our viewers Rok Lo Phal and he has asked us
some questions and we will try our best to answer those questions so
first let's
look at his questions because the
question he has asked is that when
we make a bike or car insurance claim, that is
when we make an insurance claim on our bike
or any insurance on our car, then
after making that claim whatever things are in their mind, they have
asked their questions from here and we will
try our best to answer them so definitely the first question is that what
is the settlement between this claim, that is, the second question is any solution which
stood up
after the insurance claim, that is after the insurance claim, that is
when we settle the insurance, so
after that, do
we have to pay any service to the insurance company, is there
any charge, do
we have to pay this company
or not and after that
their question is can I get old pass after these
scheme, so
after that the old parts get settled  The
parts that have changed in the insurance claim and the damaged parts, can
we take them back or not, so this is
our first
question, what is this year, which
means scrap
zone, after the insurance claim, the parts that have
changed, which have been damaged
during an accident, that part is always called scrap here,
and
in motor insurance claim, the
parts of the vehicles or bikes that are taken out,
that is called scrap, if
we initialize it, then we
get money for it in the form of salvage,
after that the second question is any soul which
stood up and of Prince Club, yes, what is it,
after taking any interest, is it always necessary to
pay it or not, now what is it that as of
today's date, in today's time,
we have to pay this amount to the company,
we did not have to pay this salvage to this company in the 80s
because the
process of insurance claim at that time was a little
different, there is no sound, what was that process earlier,  The
number of vehicles was also less
and the number of vehicles was less, so the
claims were also earned. At that time, the
insurance companies which used to believe in the past, used to get the
old and damaged passes through their own
start, they used to
tell the customer that whatever
changes you have on WhatsApp, please
send it to us through that, we will not share your huge
means with you,
firstly the liner is the customer himself,
after claiming your vehicle, whatever changes were there,
that toll was delivered to you under the
guise of, so what did this company do after delivering it, they used to
sour it there and
later sold it, now what is the
problem with this, and the problem of taking length for the big company,
Hrithik, they will have to give friend Friday Bhairav,
if it takes length, then to
make that topic, secondly, employees will have to be kept there,
security will have to be kept for the
care of the Muslims, so earlier this thing used to happen
that they used to get it through their own today, now there are 19
companies, Chakli friend, it is such a long process for
us  If we do not want to do it then after that
Infosys company said that the insurance company
said that we will always collect the dues from the customer
and will
return the old parts to the customer. Now it has been said that
when we make a claim, the insurance company charges us a salvage fee on the changes that occur in our metal
parts in the insurance claim, that is, on the
parts of some metro, this
company charges some percentage from the customer, five percent, that is,
five percent, this is seven
percent, that is, if a part worth ₹100 is installed on the show, then
this company
charges you five or seven rupees,
this 30 rupee
quit parts of trance cream on the metro parts, yes,
after the insurance claim, we
can take back our other parts, we
can keep them with us, there is no problem in this
because the insurance that we have taken is
from the same company, the
insurance claim that we have made has been made to this company, whatever
we have received in the insurance claim has been
given by this company, that is, in between  There is
no role of anyone in between means
that the dealership has no role. There are many
customers who, after buying this product, leave
their old stuff with the dealership and go away. I will
clearly tell you that
in the company, when they do not know,
without this knowledge, instead of old parts, they are
ours, then the body learns, someone is
selling them later, the dealer earns money, so
in this, if you have always done it, then
you
can take your old parts, that is, the customer can take his
old parts, there is no problem
and I hope that
you have understood this information,
these were their questions and if you have
any career question related to this information, then
you can ask us,
apart from this,
if you want to get any information related to insurance policy, insurance claim, then
you can put your question in our comment box,
we will
definitely reply to your question and
if you liked the information, then please
like and share this video and
for notification of upcoming videos  Please subscribe to the channel and
see you
in the next video, till then thanks.